<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Types on Tofu: The Varieties</title>
    <link>https://tofu.buzz/type/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Types on Tofu: The Varieties</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 21:31:25 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://tofu.buzz/type/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Silken</title>
      <link>https://tofu.buzz/silken/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 21:31:25 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tofu.buzz/silken/</guid>
      <description>what: Silken tofu is typically undrained, unpressed Japanese-style tofu with the highest water content and a custardy texture. Ultra-smooth and jiggly soft, silken tofu is most commonly used for puréeing as a base for soups, dips, and sauces. It also makes excellent dessert puddings and pie fillings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Regular</title>
      <link>https://tofu.buzz/regular/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2021 12:31:25 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tofu.buzz/regular/</guid>
      <description>what: Also called &amp;ldquo;block&amp;rdquo; tofu or &amp;ldquo;medium&amp;rdquo; tofu. Used very commonly for generic cooking purposes. It has a somewhat spongy texture and retains moisture normally, and the other types of tofu are generally labeled on the basis of their water retention.
suggested recipes: scrambles, as cubes in soups, stir-frys</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Firm Tofu</title>
      <link>https://tofu.buzz/firm/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Feb 2021 21:43:44 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tofu.buzz/firm/</guid>
      <description>what: This tofu absorbs flavors well and can be stir-fried and pan-fried (how well it will hold together depends on the brand). Think of good, seasoned firm tofu as a substitute for crumbled ricotta cheese.
suggested recipes: scrambles, cheese alternatives (block)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Extra Firm Tofu</title>
      <link>https://tofu.buzz/extrafirm/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Feb 2021 15:43:44 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tofu.buzz/extrafirm/</guid>
      <description>what: This tofu boasts of amazing shape retention and is pretty close to ground meat texture when cooked right. It&amp;rsquo;s excellent for slicing, cubing, and pan-/stir-/deep-frying, stir-frying, deep-frying. It can be baked or grilled as well.
suggested recipes: grilling recipes, substitute for cottage cheese/paneer, in-sauce stir-frys</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Super Firm Tofu</title>
      <link>https://tofu.buzz/superfirm/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Feb 2021 22:43:44 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tofu.buzz/superfirm/</guid>
      <description>what: The tofu with the least amount of water retention. Super firm tofu very dense with a high protein content, and really low moisture so it makes for quick baking/grilling recipes.
suggested recipes: grilling, cheese alternatives, stir-frys</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
